<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<projects>
    <project id="disclaiminator">
        <title>Disclaiminator</title>
        <headline>
            Single-page web app built on Object Oriented JavaScript in
            an MVC design pattern
        </headline>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    The Disclaiminator is a project for Capital One Investing that allows all of the line of business'
                    marketing disclosures to be housed in a single location.  This makes updating disclosures on all
                    marketing landing pages simple.  Due to technology constraints, all disclosures must be saved in an
                    XML file, accessed with AJAX by special javascript files on each landing page.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Managers build the javascript files within the Disclaiminator tool by selecting the disclosures they
                    need for their campaign, disclosure variables and campaign variables.  The tool then outputs a
                    javascript file to be embedded in the landing page as well as a JSON file&mdash;which can be uploaded
                    to the Disclaiminator tool to load all variables into the application for modification&mdash;and a
                    Word Document for review.
                </p>
                <p>
                    While I initially made an effort to build this application as an Angular app, I instead opted to just
                    develop it as an Object Oriented jQuery web application.
                </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
        <aside>
            <![CDATA[
                <p><b>Key Skills</b></p>
                <ul class="list">
                    <li>OOP</li>
                    <li>MV* Design</li>
                    <li>JavaScript</li>
                    <li>jQuery</li>
                    <li>HTML5/CSS3</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </aside>
    </project>
    <project id="kellyhoppen">
        <title>Kelly Hoppen Landing Page</title>
        <headline>
            Marketing landing page designed for Kelly Hoppen for apaiser during
            the launch of the new product line.
        </headline>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    This landing page was designed and developed by me within a short turn-around window for apaiser.
                    The page and associated email campaign (also designed by me) were to launch at the same time as a
                    kick-off event celebrating the partnership between celebrity designer Kelly Hoppen and apaiser.
                </p>
                <p>
                    The project, though rushed, was well received and overall, a great success.
                </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
        <aside>
            <![CDATA[
                <p><b>Key Skills</b></p>
                <ul class="list">
                    <li>Web Development</li>
                    <li>Web Design</li>
                    <li>JavaScript</li>
                    <li>jQuery</li>
                    <li>HTML5/CSS3</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </aside>
    </project>
    <project id="musicprodigy">
        <title>Music Prodigy User Flows</title>
        <headline>
            User Experience design, not "wireframe design."
        </headline>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    The Music Prodigy App was perpetually in a state of "MVP" (Minimum Viable Product), which led to many
                    User Experience challenges, since each new feature was simply tacked on without considering the overall
                    experience.  I was brought in by the company to assist with rethinking the user flow for the app and
                    help with development as well as new features and products.
                </p>
                <p>
                    As a differentiator between my work and many people who consider themselves "user experience designers,"
                    is that I approach the project from the ground up. User research, personas and identifying user flows,
                    tasks and needs are the place to start.  From there, when you get a user flow like this, expect annotations
                    for ISO standards, clear instructions and definitions of tasks.  Only then can you get into a wireframe.
                </p>
                <p>
                    An advantage I have over many UX designers is that I can also quickly prototype in code, and not just
                    garbage code, but JavaScript that can then be reused in the final application.
                </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
        <aside>
            <![CDATA[
                <p><b>Key Skills</b></p>
                <ul class="list">
                    <li>User Experience</li>
                    <li>Research</li>
                    <li>Wireframing</li>
                    <li>Design</li>
                    <li>Prototyping</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </aside>
        <images key="img/mp-userflow.jpg">
            <!-- <image>img/mp-userflow.jpg</image> -->
        </images>
    </project>
    <project id="photography">
        <title>Photography</title>
        <headline>
            I have worked in various photography fields: from product and food to
            weddings and portraits.
        </headline>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[
                <p>
                    As the owner of f/8.3 photography, I worked primarily in the wedding industry, although I was also
                    able to work in product photography for jewelry and food as well.  I also have experience working in
                    lifestyle portraits, studio photography and headshots.
                </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
        <aside>
            <![CDATA[
                <p><b>Key Skills</b></p>
                <ul class="list">
                    <li>Photography</li>
                    <li>Lighting</li>
                    <li>Photoshop</li>
                    <li>Lightroom</li>
                    <li>Studio Management</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </aside>
    </project>
</projects>